Philip Benn

Oakland, CA 94611 | 310-403-1826 | philipaldenbenn@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/philip-benn-5977142

Digital Artist/3D Production/Generative AI

Digital Artist with a background in 3D production for product rendering and animation. Expert knowledge of Generative AI with an emphasis 3D and image diffusion machine learning pipelines for image and video. Excellent written and verbal communication skills and problem-solving abilities. An outgoing and personable team member.

Areas of Expertise

3D Production and Product Rendering: Adobe Creative Suite, Cinema4D, Maya, Rhino, Nuke, Blender | **Generative AI:** Stable Diffusion, ComfyUI, Automatic1111 | **Web Development:** VSCode, Python, JAMstack web development architecture

Links

Portfolio and Blog: https://benn-portfolio.vercel.com GenAI: https://www.novelspace.tech Cool demo web app: https://elysium.novelspace.tech

Experience

NovelSpace 2023

Art Director and Developer

Designed and Developed full stack web apps integrating LLMs, Stable Diffusion Txt2img ML models. See links above.

Logitech 2019 – 2023

Staff lead Visual Designer

Created and executed workflows for marketing assets. Worked with Engineering, Industrial Designers, Product Managers.

- Served as a project lead of four years of product launches for the mobility team.
- Created 3D Rendering, 2D Design Visualization.
- Performed CAD data conversion into DCC renderable assets.
- Created photorealistic imagery for Logitech website, in-store POS, packaging, and partner websites.

Schawk 2017 – 2018

Staff 3D Technical Director

Created digital image assets for Apple product refresh and launch events.

• Executed Workflow for digital asset production of high-resolution, photorealistic imagery for product launches and in-store POS.

Nvidia 2014 – 2017

Staff 3D Technical Director

Created digital image assets for Nvidia events and product launches.

- Researched and developed off-line and real-time GPU rendering pipelines.
- Performed product testing for Nvidia's in-house GPU progressive and programmable renderer.
- Created workflows for CAD data conversion into DCC renderable assets.

California College of Art

Taught motion studio and MFA exhibition courses.

Philip Benn

philipaldenbenn@gmail.com

Page Two

Additional Relevant Experience

Prologue Films, Technical Director | Visual Designer | Staff | Contractor
Eveo
Hydraulx
Atmospheric
R/GA

School of Visual Arts, Computer Art Adjunct
Taught courses in 3D computer graphics.

Virginia Commonwealth University, Design Department Adjunct Taught courses in computer graphics and animation.

Education

Master of Fine Arts (MFA), Design Technology
San Francisco Art Institute
Bachelor of Arts (BA), English Literature
Virginia Commonwealth University